<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cycling And Travel Posts on Md. Taufique Hussain</title>
    <link>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cycling And Travel Posts on Md. Taufique Hussain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity Review 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/2017-12-31-activity-review-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/2017-12-31-activity-review-2017/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of 2017. So it&amp;rsquo;s time to review my activities of 2017. It&amp;rsquo;s time to review how far I could achieve what I intended to achieve this year. It was kind of a memorable year for me in terms of my activity. Probably the most active year for me. So, I thought I should write a post about my feelings. I want to start with a infographic that summarizes my 2017 activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josshila 196 - Rohitpur, Keraniganj</title>
      <link>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/2017-12-09-josshila_196/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/2017-12-09-josshila_196/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 5:40am in the morning. And immediately tried to get some more sleep as I thought I had a little chance to catch up the Josshila group. But getting more sleep had to wait as it was hurting me to miss the ride what was supposed to be my last BDCyclists Josshila Saturday for 2017. After getting out with the bike, found out that there was some rain last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josshila 195 - Purbachal Off-Roads</title>
      <link>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/2017-12-02-josshila_195/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.taufique.me/cycling_and_travel/2017-12-02-josshila_195/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while I am riding an MTB but never before I have gone for a proper off-road ride. There were several Josshila-Saturday events to the off-roads of Purbachal and Rupganj. But my mud-phobia prevented me to join those. As it&amp;rsquo;s winter, thought there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be much mud at this time of the year. So I took this chance.

The sun was just rising. We found a thick layer of fog just above the ground as soon as we left the congested area of Dhaka and moved to the countyside.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>